{
    "subject": "resource/William_S._Burroughs",
    "predicate": "ontology/movement",
    "object": "resource/Beat_Generation",
    "human_readable": "The movement associated with William S. Burroughs is the Beat Generation.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.833101749420166,
            "question": "What literary movement is William S. Burroughs associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7841718792915344,
            "question": "William S. Burroughs's work is often associated with which literary movement?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7365315556526184,
            "question": "What literary movement did William S. Burroughs contribute to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6518640518188477,
            "question": "Name the literary movement that Burroughs was part of."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6487669348716736,
            "question": "To which generation of writers does William S. Burroughs belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6084586977958679,
            "question": "William S. Burroughs is considered a key figure in which literary movement?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4065302312374115,
            "question": "What was the Beat Generation known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.04551779106259346,
            "question": "What is the name of the literary movement known for its nonconformist ideas and experimentation?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.0445670485496521,
            "question": "Which literary movement emerged in the 1950s and featured writers like Jack Kerouac and Allen Ginsberg?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.023890042677521706,
            "question": "Which generation of writers challenged traditional norms and explored themes of alienation and social change?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The movement associated with William S. Burroughs is the Beat Generation.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8392_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which literary movement emerged in the 1950s and featured writers like Jack Kerouac and Allen Ginsberg?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8392_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the literary movement known for its nonconformist ideas and experimentation?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8392_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the Beat Generation known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8392_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8392_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8392_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8392_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8392_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8392_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8392_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8392_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8392_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8392_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8392_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the Beat Generation and its association with writers like William S. Burroughs, Allen Ginsberg, and Jack Kerouac. Therefore, it supports the statement that the movement associated with William S. Burroughs is the Beat Generation."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}